迈克 · 诺斯: 第三次传球时你要做的第三件事是小传球
&gt;&gt; Mike North: The third thing you're
going to do as the third pass is in small
因为一次性完成这个任务是没有好处的。
chunks because there's really no benefit
to doing this in a huge single pass.
您将打开严格的打字稿编译器设置。
You're going to turn on strict
TypeScript compiler settings.
所以严格的空检查，使它成为这样
So the strict null checks,
that makes it so
这个 null 没有被考虑，对不起，我不想用双重否定。
that null it's not regarded, sorry I
don't wanna use a double negative here.
将 strict null 检查设置为 false，null
With strict null checks set to false, null
被视为任何类型的有效值。
is regarded as a valid value in any type.
不是任何类型，但是可以有一个值为 null 的数字。
Not the any type, but you could
have a number whose value is null.
所以 null 适用于任何地方。
So null fits anywhere.
严格的 null 检查，设置为 true，使它成为 true
Strict null check,
set to true, makes it so
唯一能够保持无效的东西就是 null。
that the only thing that
can hold the null is null.
从那时起你就开始摇摆不定,
And that's where you're
gonna start shaking out,
返回 null 的代码分支，现在你必须开始引入
branches of your code that returned null
and now you'll have to start introducing
这个函数的交集运算符返回字符串或 null。
the intersection operator with this
function returns the string or null.
严格的真实开启了一系列严格的设置，我不会深入讨论这个问题。
Strict true turns on a bunch of strictness
settings, I won't go too deeply into that.
严格的函数类型验证参数和
Strict function types it
validates arguments and
回调类型的返回类型。
return types of callback types.
所以如果你说,
So if you say,
我使用 mouseListener 函数作为参数，strictFunctionTypes 将
I take a mouseListener function as
an argument, strictFunctionTypes will
更严格的类型匹配来对抗你试图传递给它的任何东西。
more rigorously type match against
everything you try to pass to it.
和 Bind，Call，Apply，我们已经看过了,
And Bind, Call, Apply,
we've already looked at,
确保传递给函数 bind、 call 和
that makes sure that the arguments
passed to function bind, call, and
适当应用和词法范围的所有类型检查。
apply and the lexical scope
all type check appropriately.
通常，如果没有将最后一个标志设置为 true、 bind、 call 和 apply,
And normally, without that last flag
set to true, bind, call, and apply,
你基本上失去了所有类型的安全，通过进入这些功能。
you basically lose all type safety
through going into those functions.
所以这就是你试图摆脱尽可能多的明确 anys，你可以和
So this is where you're trying to get rid
of as many explicit anys as you can and
用更有意义的类型替换它们。
replace them with more meaningful types.
你要避免选角，这就是你现在的处境
And you wanna avoid casting,
which is where you're
强迫打字脚本将某种东西视为特定的类型。
forcing TypeScript to regard
something as a particular type.
这是用 as 关键字完成的，所以你会说，把它看作一个字符串。
That is done with the as keyword, so
you'd say, regard this as a string.
你在你的应用中引入的东西越多,
The more of that you
introduce into your app,
你们这种人越有机会撒谎。
the more your types have
a chance of lying to.
演讲者1: 我的意思是,
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: So I mean,
提升现有代码库到打字稿的好处是什么？
what is the benefit of uplifting
an existing code base to TypeScript?
首先使用打字稿也有同样的好处。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: They are the same benefits
of using TypeScript in the first place.
演讲者1: 你所说的工作量，以及
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: The amount of
work you are talking about, and
这样能证明这些好处是正当的吗？
does that justify those benefits?
迈克 · 诺斯: 所以这有点取决于个案的基础。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: So
it kinda depends on a case-by-case basis.
比如说,
For example,
如果你谈论的是一些非常小的 JavaScript 模块
if you're talking about some of these
really small JavaScript modules that do
一件事，只有一件事，左垫是一个很好的例子，对不对？
one thing and one thing only, left pad
would be a good example of this, right?
它在字符串的开头添加了一定数量的空白,
It's adding a prescribed amount of white
space to the beginning of the string,
我不确定把这种东西转换成
I'm not sure there's a whole lot of value
in converting that kind of thing to
打字稿。
TypeScript.
但是，如果您想在其他地方对代码使用 TypeScript
However, if you want to use
TypeScript elsewhere on code
缺乏类型，必须有人提供类型信息。
that is lacking types, someone has
to provide that type information.
你有两个选择，或者你可以，通过我稍后给你看的东西,
You have two choices, you either can,
through something I'll show you later,
比如说，把这整个模块当成任何东西，任何东西。
say, regard this whole module as an any,
like anything goes.
当我从这个模块导入一些东西时，让我做我想做的事情。
When I import something from this module,
let me do whatever I want.
你可以这样做，但是这样做是有风险的，因为在其他地方这样做也是有风险的。
You could do that but that's risky for
the same reason any is a risky elsewhere.
另一个选择是你的图书馆的每一个消费者
The other option is every consumer
of your library has to kind of
填写类型信息，至少是他们希望使用的部分。
fill in the type information, at least for
the portion they wish to use.
因为编译器正在执行一个整体
Because the compiler it
is performing a holistic
分析你的应用程序，包括所有的依赖性。
analysis of your app,
which includes all of it's dependencies.
所以，缺少类型信息
So, missing type information for
依赖关系会导致任何依赖于该代码的应用程序的弱点。
dependencies that causes weakness in
any app that depends on that code.